They took the sledgehammer of Capitol
Hill. Trump's in a room pumping a pills.
Must tweets laws from a private jet says
democracy's dead, but we're not there
yet. Education. Yeah, they torch the
schools, replace teachers with clickbait
and crypto fools. Kids learn more from
Tik Tok feeds than a thousand
bureaucratic PhD. We're circling the
train in a limousine. Let billionaires
with GS freeze your funds to gold and
break. Come verify it or fade away. We
got tariffs on air. Taxes on dreams
outrage inflation in the land of the
meat. Is this dystopia or just routine?
Is freedom baby for the ultra scene?
Remember when facts had a little more
weight? Now it's true soul served on a
gold dinner plate. Congress is streaming
on only fans and the nukes are action up
to the highest stand. Border walls built
from my phone screens and I see drones
fly by red bull machines. Nol sold to
Tesla's brand because laws is the backup
just not for your fam. Well folks in
today America and you can privatize a
prison but not your grandma. So guitar
squeak
market unless you're broke. We're
suggest
[Music]
we got tariffs on love. Taxes on raise a
post go into days. You ain't for B crowd
still does she and freedom baby in a
fascist regime like that Molotov with
your last receipt. Tell the SEC to kiss
both cheeks. If it all goes down in a
blaze of tweets, we'll be moshing in the
streets with bump beats.
It's not worth show. No gods, no one.
The algorithm judges what's left of our
rights while we're all doomed scrolling
through endless fights. Corporated
bailouts are raining down while private
yachts in a sinking town. The working
class gets a pat on the back. Essential
heroes, but your pensions hacked. So
raise a middle finger to the status quo.
When the rich man system starts to blow,
we're circling the drain in a limousine
led by billionaires with GMTs. Freeze
your funds if you're old and great. Come
verified it or just decay. We got
tariffs on love, taxes on raise a post
true gospel in days.